
Quan Ly
Marketing Staff
Date of birth:  30/04/1990
Gender:  F
Phone:  0123 333 4668
Email:  riskoperator@gmail.com
Address:  5 Lang Ha, Hanoi

OBJECTIVE
A position of professional marketer, work in an active environment with precious opportunities for career advancement. To be a CMO in the future.

EDUCATION
Sep 2010 - Jan 2014
National Economics University
Major in Marketing Adminitration

EXPERIENCE
Jan 2014 - Now
FPT Trade
Marketing Director staff
- Create marketing plans for promoting new product launches.
- Implement promotion programs to push sales volume.
- Recruit PGs for promotion programs.
- Manage and follow up with distributors.
- Consolidate sales volume info from Sales Supervisor and Area Sales Manager.
- Prepare weekly & monthly sales reports to Sales Manager.

SKILLS
Creative thinkings
- Be able to give unique & reliable ideas for Campaigns, contribute to success of these campaign.
Computer
- Competent with most Microsoft Office programmes such as Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook.
- Experience with Online Marketing tools such as: Facebook Ads, Google Adword and SEO 

LINGUISTICS
Good at English

ACTIVITIES
Jan 2012 - Dec 2013
Marketing Club
President
- Make plan of activities in a year for the club.
- Execute all the activities by giving the directions & control the processing.
- Contact, negotiate, cooperate with sponsors and other clubs in National Economics University.

CERTIFICATIONS AND AWARDS
July 2014
Bachelor in Marketing at National Economics University
Jan 2014
Toeic 650 by IIG Viet Nam
July 22, 2012
Third Pride in "Star up with Kawaii" competition.